[{"question": "Choose a C Conditional Operator from the list.", "option1": "A) ?:", "option2": "B) :?", "option3": "C) :<", "option4": "D) <:", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "What is the other name for C Language ?: Question Mark Colon Operator.?", "option1": "A) Comparison Operator", "option2": "B) If-Else Operator", "option3": "C) Binary Operator", "option4": "D) Ternary Operator", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Choose a syntax for C Ternary Operator from the list.", "option1": "A) condition ? expression1 : expression2", "option2": "B) condition :\u00a0expression1 ?\u00a0expression2", "option3": "C) condition ?\u00a0expression1 <\u00a0expression2", "option4": "D) condition <\u00a0expression1 ?\u00a0expression2", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "What is the output of the C statement.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=0;\n    a = 5<2 ? 4 : 3;\n    printf(\"%d\",a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 4", "option2": "B) 3", "option3": "C) 5", "option4": "D) 2", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=0;\n    a = printf(\"4\");\n    printf(\"%d\",a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 04", "option2": "B) compiler error", "option3": "C) 40", "option4": "D) 41", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=0;\n    a = 5>2 ? printf(\"4\"): 3;\n    printf(\"%d\",a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) compiler error", "option2": "B) 14", "option3": "C) 41", "option4": "D) 0", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=0;\n    a = (5>2) ? : 8;\n    printf(\"%d\",a);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 0", "option2": "B) 1", "option3": "C) 8", "option4": "D) compiler error", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=0, b;\n    a = (5>2) ? b=6: b=8;\n    printf(\"%d %d\",a, b);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 6 6", "option2": "B) 0 6", "option3": "C) 0 8", "option4": "D) compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Choose a correct statement regarding C Comparison Operators.", "option1": "A) (x == y)\u00a0Is x really equal to y.\n(x != y)\u00a0Is x not equal to y.", "option2": "B) (x < y) Is x less than y\n(x > y) Is x greater than y", "option3": "C) (x <= y) Is x less than or equal to y.\n(x >= y) Is x greater than or equal to y", "option4": "D) All the above", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " Choose a statement to use C If Else statement.", "option1": "A) else if is compulsory to use with if statement.", "option2": "B) else is compulsory to use with if statement.", "option3": "C) else or else if is optional with if statement.", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " Choose a correct C Statement using IF Conditional Statement.", "option1": "A) if( condition )\n{\n    //statements;\n}\n", "option2": "B) if( condition )\n{\n    //statements;\n}\nelse\n{\n    //statements;\n}\n", "option3": "C) if( condition1 )\n{\n    //statements;\n}\nelse if( condition2)\n{\n    //statements;\n}\nelse\n{\n    //statements;\n}\n", "option4": "D) All the above.", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    if( 4 > 5 )\n    {\n        printf(\"Hurray..\\n\");\n    }\n     printf(\"Yes\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) Yes", "option2": "B) Hurray..\nYes", "option3": "C) Hurray..Yes", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    if( 4 > 5 )\n        printf(\"Hurray..\\n\");\n        printf(\"Yes\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) Yes", "option2": "B) Hurray..\nYes", "option3": "C) Hurray..Yes", "option4": "D) No Output", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    if( 4 < 5 )\n        printf(\"Hurray..\\n\");\n        printf(\"Yes\");\n    else\n        printf(\"England\")\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) Hurray..Yes", "option2": "B) Hurray..\nYes", "option3": "C) Compiler error", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    if( 10 < 9 )\n        printf(\"Hurray..\\n\");\n    else if(4 > 2)\n        printf(\"England\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) England", "option2": "B) Hurray..", "option3": "C) Compiler error for missing else", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    if( 10 > 9 )\n        printf(\"Singapore\\n\");\n    else if(4%2 == 0)\n        printf(\"England\\n\");\n        printf(\"Poland\");\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) Singapore", "option2": "B) Singapore\nPoland", "option3": "C) Singapore\nEngland\nPoland", "option4": "D) England\nPoland", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    if(-5)\n    {\n        printf(\"Germany\\n\");\n    }\n    if(5)\n    {\n        printf(\"Texas\\n\");\n    }\n    printf(\"ZING\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) ZING", "option2": "B) Texas\nZING", "option3": "C) Germany\nTexas\nZING", "option4": "D) Compiler error as a number can not be put as condition inside IF.", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of the C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    if(10.0)\n    {\n        printf(\"Texas\\n\");\n    }\n    printf(\"ZING\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) ZING", "option2": "B) Texas\nZING", "option3": "C) Compiler error.", "option4": "D) None of the above.", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    if(\"abc\")\n    {\n        printf(\"India\\n\");\n    }\n    if('c')\n    {\n        printf(\"Honey\\n\");\n    }\n    printf(\"ZING\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) ZING", "option2": "B) Honey\nZING", "option3": "C) India\nZING", "option4": "D) India\nHoney\nZING", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    if(TRUE)\n    {\n        printf(\"India\\n\");\n    }\n    if(true)\n    {\n        printf(\"Honey\\n\");\n    }\n    printf(\"ZING\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) India\nZING", "option2": "B) Honey\nZING", "option3": "C) India\nHoney\nZING", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}]
